-=聖城家園SCG字幕組 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
僅供翻譯交流使用, 禁止用於商業用途
協調: 瀟妹紙
翻譯: 咳嗽的小魚 Young 撈鹽 沒看過的一橫 噹噹要變瘦 尤蘭達子 曉笛 袋蜀
校對: 影子
西班牙 加那利群島
Senor O'Conner, senor O'Conner!
奧康納先生 奧康納先生!
快! 快來!
快! 這邊! 這邊!
沒事 讓我來
It's okay, you're just in time.
沒事 你來的正是時候
You're going to be a great father, Brian.
布萊恩 你會是個很棒的父親
What makes you so sure?
你就這麼有把握?
Because I'll be there to kick your ass if you ain't.
因為要是你做得不好 我就揍你
- Get in there.  - Go.
- 快進去吧  - 快
Brian.
布萊恩
Remember, the second you go through those doors,
記住 一旦你跨入那道門
everything changes.
一切都不一樣了
Our old life is done.
過去的日子已經結束
Let's go for a little ride.
一起去飆車吧
速度與激情6
莫斯科
- Special Agent Hobbs?  - Riley Hicks.
- 霍布斯探員?  - 你是萊麗·希克斯
I read your file. Top of your class at FLETC.
我看了你的檔案 聯邦執法訓練班的精英
Cairo, Tunis.
執行過開羅和突尼斯的任務
Youngest RSO ever in Afghanistan.
阿富汗戰場上最年輕的特種兵
Hell, if you're half as good as you are on paper,
聽著 只要你有紙上說的一半那麼好
we're going to get along just fine.
我們准能合得來
A Russian military caravan attacked,
一輛俄羅斯軍車被襲
satellite component stolen.
衛星關鍵部件被盜
Cars just came out of nowhere.
敵方車輛不知道從哪竄出來的
Six hospitalized, a dozen vehicles destroyed.
6人受傷住院 十幾輛車被毀
All that in under 90 seconds, in and out.
整個過程只用了90秒 幹淨利落
This is world-class.
這是世界級的水准
Job this good, there's only one crew in the world
全世界上只有一隊人
who could get this done.
能幹得這麼漂亮
How the hell did that get up there?
那車是怎麼上去的?
They caught one.
警方逮到了一個人
Where?
在哪?
國際刑警總部
I got you five minutes with this guy.
你有5分鍾審問這家夥
I only need two.
2分鍾就夠了
I want your boss. Where's Shaw?
我要找你老大 肖在哪?
I ain't telling you shit.
我什麼都不會告訴你
I was hoping you'd say that.
希望你別後悔
Is that legal?
這麼做合法嗎?
No.
不合法
But are you going to go in there and tell him?
難道你打算進去告訴他?
I've got rights, you asshole!
我是受法律保護的 混蛋!
Not today.
今天例外
No, no!
不 不要!
- Well, is he talking?  - Not anymore.
- 他招了嗎?  - 什麼都沒說
That room is bugged, Hobbs.
那房間裝了竊聽器 霍布斯
So, any information you just beat out of him, Interpol has now.
你從他那打聽到的情報 國際刑警都知道了
Great. Now they can take the morning off. Shaw's in London.
很好 他們早上可以休息了 肖在倫敦
Let's go pick him up.
我們去抓他
Woman, you just don't pick up Owen Shaw like he's groceries.
姑娘 肖可不是隨便就能抓到的
If you want to catch wolves, you need wolves.
如果你想逮住狼群 你需要同樣的狼群
Let's go hunting.
狩獵開始
This is what 100 million buys?
花一個億就買了這玩意?
It wasn't that hard to find you, Toretto.
托雷托 找到你並不費勁
I wasn't hiding.
我又沒藏起來
How's the life of the retired international criminal?
國際罪犯的退休生活怎樣?
I like it here. It's quiet.
我喜歡這裏 很安靜
Nice weather,
天氣不錯
and no extradition.
也不用怕被引渡
So what are you doing here, cop?
你來這做什麼 警官?
Last Tuesday, a team of highly coordinated drivers
上周二 一隊精英車手
took down an entire military convoy in Russia.
在俄羅斯襲擊了一輛軍用車
I don't do cold weather.
我不喜歡冰天雪地的
I know it wasn't you.
我知道不是你幹的
But you're going to help me catch the team responsible.
但你得幫我抓住那夥人
And you ain't gonna need that.
你也不用拿槍出來
You can't touch him, Hobbs. You've got no powers...
你不能抓他 霍布斯 你無權...
I'm not here to extradite anyone.
我不是來這抓人的
See, he's going to come voluntarily.
聽著 他自己會來找我的
As a matter of fact,
事實上
he's going to beg me.
他會來求我
This was taken a week ago.
這是一周前拍的
I'll see you out front.
我去前門等你
It's Letty, isn't it?
是萊蒂 對嗎?
It's impossible.
這不可能
If that was my husband, if there was a chance, no matter how small,
換了是我 如果還有一線希望 不管多渺茫
I would go.
我都會去
I'm going to need everything, all the info you got.
我需要所有信息 包括你查到的一切
You'll get it when the team gets it.
隊伍到齊了 就自然會給你
No team.
沒有團隊了
This is going to have to be me alone.
這回我自己單幹
It's not that simple.
事情沒那麼簡單
The crew we're after, they hit like thunder and disappear like smoke.
我們想找的這夥人 他們來無影去無蹤
You go in alone, you won't ever touch them.
就你一人 碰到別想碰到他們
I've been chasing this guy across four continents and 12 countries,
我已經跨越4州 12個國家追捕他們了
and believe me, the last damn place I want to be right now
相信我 要是萬不得已 我可不會厚著臉皮
is on your front doorstep, selling Girl Scout cookies.
站在你家門口來找你幫忙
I need your help, Dom.
我需要你的幫助 唐
I need your team.
我需要你的團隊
Okay, ladies, bring it in.
好的 女士們 都拿著
Listen, I want to make a toast.
聽著 我想先幹一杯
Come on.
快過來
Listen, I know a few of y'all have already been to Macau,
我知道你們中有人已經去過澳門了
but you have never seen the town
但只有跟著我
till you've seen it through my eyes.
你們才會真正了解這城市
We got a penthouse suite
我有間帶海景的頂樓套房
with an ocean view that's going to change your life.
它將顛覆你們的人生
150-foot yacht with a helicopter pad...
150英尺的遊艇 還有直升機停機坪...
Mmm-hmm. Safe to say, you're about to have the time of your lives.
負責任的說 這將是你們畢生難忘的經曆
No, you are.
不 你才是
Cheers.
幹杯
夥計 瞧瞧你 開著法拉利 兜裏大把的鈔票!
哥們 以前你可是當代羅賓漢 有錢大家一起花
你知道我什麼意思
錢改變了你
你說得沒錯
錢的確改變了我
我意識到了錢又不是長在樹上的
是從天而降的!
謝謝... 看起來很好吃
Nice!
不錯嘛!
I'm a citizen of the world.
我四海為家
Ever thought about settling down?
有沒有想過安頓下來?
Starting a life together?
和我一起開始新的生活?
Aren't we doing that?
我們現在不是嗎?
Are we?
是嗎?
把槍放下... 現在!!!
Hello?
喂?
Dom?
唐?
I'll be there.
我馬上過去
Hey, my man, I need you to turn this plane around.
嘿 老兄 馬上把飛機掉個頭
All right, listen, ladies. There's been a little change of plans.
好的 女士們 聽著 我們的計劃有些小變動
Something came up.
有點事情要處理
You know that casino I was telling you all about?
還記得我說過的那個俱樂部嗎?
I got some vouchers
我有幾張自助餐的
to the buffet.
餐券
What do you think of this?
覺得這個怎樣?
He likes it. All right.
他喜歡 很好
Yes.
好的
Or this?
這個呢?
Yes.
他也喜歡
That's my boy. All right, let's see how this thing flies.
不愧是我兒子 來 瞧瞧這個怎麼飛的
Are you watching?
你看著嗎?
It's Uncle Dom. What do you know?
是唐叔叔 你認識嗎?
Are you waving? What up'?
你在打招呼嗎? 什麼事?
Hey, Jack.
嘿 傑克
What's up, Uncle Dom? What's up, Uncle Dom?
近來可好 唐叔叔? 別來無恙?
You excited to see him?
見到他很開心嗎?
Are you already pushing imports on him?
是你讓他選的進口車嗎?
You say, "Dad's not pushing anything."
快告訴叔叔 "爸爸他可沒逼我"
He chose that car.
他自己選的車
We know he's an O'Conner, but,
我們都知道他姓奧康納
I brought you something, Jack.
不過傑克 我給你帶了點禮物
- Yeah! He's also a Toretto.  - I don't know.
- 太好啦! 他也是托雷托家的一份子  - 我可不這麼想
Luckily, he has a couple more years to decide, right'?
幸運的是 他還有好多年來做決定 對嗎?
I think he decided, Mia.
我覺得他已經想好了 米婭
I think it's time for his nap.
到他睡午覺的時間了
Come on, baby. Okay.
過來 寶貝 好的
Say bye.
說再見
It's weird, huh?
有點怪 對嗎?
What's weird?
什麼挺怪的?
We got everything.
我們擁有一切
You know, down to the beer and the barbeque.
比如啤酒 燒烤什麼的
But it just...
但是...
I don't know, it just doesn't feel like home.
我也不知道 就是感覺不像家
Maybe it's because, uh,
也許是因為
you don't realize how much you appreciate something
總要等到失去了
until somebody takes it away.
才知道珍貴
I don't know.
我也說不清
The place has probably changed so much,
也許這裏變化太大了
you wouldn't even recognize it anymore.
都快認不出來了
Yeah.
是的
Everything's changed.
一切都變了
So what's up with you? What's going on?
你怎麼來了? 出了什麼事?
Taken a week ago.
一周前拍的
Diplomatic Security Service.
外交安全局
Hobbs.
是霍布斯
You know, I used to do this shit all the time as a cop.
要知道 以前我幹警察的時候也常用這種手段
This is exactly what cops do. He's messing with your head.
警察就是這樣 他想把你弄暈
Letty's dead, Dom.
萊蒂已經死了 唐
I need to know for sure.
我需要搞清楚
Then I'm going with you.
我和你一起去
You said you were going to leave this life behind.
你說過要告別過去那種生活
We both said that we were leaving the life behind.
我們都說過這話
He's right.
他說得沒錯
We're family.
我們是一家人
If we got a problem, we deal with it together.
有問題 我們一起應對
And I'll feel safer knowing you're both out there,
你們倆一起行動 互相照應
watching each other's backs.
我更放心
You're stronger together. You always were.
並肩作戰更強大 你們一向如此
Now go get Letty.
去把萊蒂帶回來
倫敦
Bring her home.
帶她回家
Thank God!
謝天謝地!
Finally, some equipment I can work with.
終於有像樣的裝備了
What up, boy?
還好嗎 兄弟?
This is way better than that trash in Rio.
這比裏約的那推垃圾強多了
Way better.
強多了
You sure about these guys?
你確定他們能行嗎?
Nope.
不確定
Has anybody heard from Leo or Santos?
有人知道萊昂和桑托斯的消息嗎?
Last time anyone saw them, they were hitting up the casinos in Monte Carlo.
最近一次有人看到他們是在蒙特卡洛賭場
I thought that was our last job, Brian.
布萊恩 我以為從那以後我們金盆洗手了呢
And who's paying for all this equipment? The taxpayers?
誰給買的這些裝備? 納稅人?
So now we work for The Hulk? That's what we're doing?
我們現在為綠巨人賣力了? 那就是我們的工作?
Why do I smell baby oil?
我怎麼聞到一股嬰兒潤膚油的味道?
If you keep running your piehole,
你的臭嘴再胡說八道
you're going to smell an ass-kicking.
你就要挨揍了
All right, Hobbs,
好吧 霍布斯
you got the best crew in the world
站在你面前的
standing right in front of you.
是世界上最厲害的團隊
Give them a reason to stay.
給他們一個留下的理由
Our target is Owen Shaw.
我們的目標是歐文·肖
Former major in the S.A.S., Spec-ops soldier.
原英國特種空勤隊的少校 特種兵
He ran the UK's Mobility Division in Kabul and Basra.
他曾在喀布爾和巴士拉領導英軍的機動師
Ah, damn. That Mobility unit's the truth.
該死 那支機動師不是蓋的
We're talking vehicular warfare. Best in the world.
他們的車輪戰術世界一流
- You got some chips?  - Those guys don't mess around.
- 還有薯片嗎?  - 他們可不是吃幹飯的
For years, they've been running jobs in Europe,
近年來 他們一直在歐洲活動
but it's their most recent jobs
這些是他們最近幹的幾票
that graduated them to a whole new level.
水平大有提高
Three targets, highly specific.
三個目標非常明確
The program terminal from an ICBM missile...
洲際導彈程序終端...
Got a little change?
有零錢嗎?
Seriously? You're a millionaire,
開玩笑啊? 你都是百萬富翁了
and you're still trying to ask for money?
你卻還向別人要錢?
That's how you stay a millionaire.
百萬富翁就是這麼省出來的
So what does this all mean?
這些是什麼情況?
Well, our best guess is that Shaw's crew
我們預測很有可能是肖他們
is building a Nightshade device.
正在建造一種龍葵裝備
- Which is?  - A tech bomb.
- 那是什麼?  - 一種高科技炸彈
Designed to block an entire military communication grid
可以阻斷整個軍隊的通訊系統
for 24 hours.
長達24小時
If you blind a soldier for a single second
如果士兵在戰場上失明哪怕一秒鍾
in the middle of a fight, he dies.
他死定了
If you blind a country for 24 hours,
如果整個國家的通訊系統癱瘓24小時
the loss of life is unthinkable.
很難想象多少人會喪命
This could be worth billions to the right buyer.
這種裝備對合適的買家來說可值幾十億
Billions?
幾十億?
Why don't we just steal that shit?
我們幹嘛不把那玩意偷來?
Hey, man.
兄弟們
Which one of these things is a dollar?
這裏面哪個是一美元?
It says something about...
這裏說...
It's on the house.
我請客
I want you to help me catch Shaw.
我想讓你們幫我抓住肖
He's only got one piece left that he needs,
他還差一步就大功告成了
and I intend to stop him before he gets it.
我要在他成功之前阻止他
Now, I know you guys are a family.
我知道你們親如一家
So I'm offering you a chance right now
那我現在就給你們一個機會
to make that family whole again.
讓你們重新團聚
You want to make this family whole again?
你想讓這個家重新團聚嗎?
Get us to Letty, we'll get you Shaw,
帶我們找到萊蒂 我們就幫你抓到肖
full pardons all the way around.
還要赦免我們所有人
I can't promise you that.
這個我不能向你保證
Yes, you can.
必須保證
That's the deal.
這就是條件
Take it or leave it.
接受或者離開
You get me Shaw,
你們幫我逮到肖
and I'll get your pardons.
你們就全部赦免
You heard him.
你們聽到他說的了
But this is different.
這次不一樣
We're not dealing with cops,
我們不是對付警察
we're not dealing with drug dealers.
不是對付毒販
This is a whole different level.
這次完全不同
We're getting paid, right?
這活兒有酬勞的 對吧?
Interpol picked up one of Shaw's guys in Moscow.
國際刑警在莫斯科抓到了一個肖的手下
I went in, had a little therapy session with him.
我進去審了他一會
He gave up Shaw's hideout.
他供出了肖藏身的地方
Then why aren't we down there now?
那現在我們為什麼不去那啊?
Well, we weren't invited.
我們沒收到邀請
Hobbs, they're sending in your punching bag.
霍布斯 他們派你的出氣筒進去了
He's wired. He's going to give a positive ID on Shaw before they move in.
他身上帶有通訊設備 等他確認了肖的身份 警察就會沖進去
So, the cops just let you go, huh?
警察就這麼放你走了?
Don't worry, I didn't give them shit.
別擔心 我什麼也沒說
Oh, I'm not worried.
我不擔心
Okay.
好了
Turn it over for me.
幫我啟動它
God, it's amazing.
天啊 太棒了
The simplest things can cause the biggest problems.
一個小零件也可能引發很大的問題
Good news is, if you swap out a bad part,
好消息是 如果你把壞的零件換下來
everything runs smooth as silk again.
一切便順暢如初了
Look, Shaw...
聽著 肖...
Wait, Shaw! Shaw!
等等 肖! 肖!
Shaw!
肖!
I just got confirmation on Shaw. They're going in.
我已經確認是肖 他們沖進去了
Wait, wait, hold up...
等等 等等 慢...
Police scanners are saying alarms are going off at Interpol headquarters.
警用電台說國際刑警總部的警報響了
Shit.
該死
He brought us here so he could take down Interpol.
他把我們引來這裏 就是為了對付國際刑警
This whole thing's a set-up.
整件事就是個陷阱
- Brian, take the team.  - What about you?
- 布萊恩 你帶隊  - 你呢?
Hobbs and I will wait for Shaw.
我和霍布斯在這兒等肖
Shaw leads to Letty.
跟著肖就能找到萊蒂
Come on, you son of a bitch.
快出來 混蛋
What's this?
這是什麼?
It's your share from the last job.
這是你上次任務的酬勞
You're part of the team, Oakes.
你也是團隊的一員 歐克斯
You do your job, you get paid.
你幹活了 就會有酬勞
There's a little extra in there for you.
多給了你一些
Consider it an advance.
就當是預付的酬勞
For what?
預付?
The next job, of course.
當然是下次任務的錢
Which job?
什麼任務?
The one we're working right now.
就是我們現在在做的這個
Han, how far are we from Interpol?
韓 我們離國際刑警總部有多遠?
Twelve blocks away.
12個街區
You guys, it's a ghost town over here.
兄弟們 這裏連個鬼影都沒有
Shaw must have pulled all the cops to him.
肖肯定是把全部警察都引到他那去了
All right, y'all, we're in this shit, so let's go get it.
好了 各位 反正我們接了這活兒 就全力以赴吧
It's been fun running with you, mate.
和你合作很愉快 夥計
Stop! Drop the bag!
別動! 放下提包!
- There he is.  - On it.
- 他在那  - 看到了
Toretto, it's on you. Straight ahead, don't lose him.
托雷托 靠你了 他在你正前方 別跟丟了
Ain't gonna happen.
不可能跟丟的
Sorry about that, boys.
抱歉了 兄弟們
Interpol, straight ahead.
國際刑警總部就在正前方
Let's go, guys. We've got company.
出發了 夥計們 有人來了
Let's go, boys.
快走
Get in! Let's go!
上車! 快走!
Hey! We got to move. Now!
嘿! 我們得走了 快點!
- Shaw, we have three cars tailing us.  - You know what to do.
- 肖 有三輛車跟著我們  - 你知道該怎麼做
芯控槍准備 快
Guys, I got the Rover.
兄弟們 我來對付這輛路虎
Okay, I got...
好吧 我對付...
Whatever the hell that thing is.
不管是什麼鳥東西
What is that, a hockey puck?
那是什麼 冰球嗎?
全部擊中!
一號芯片就緒
Oh, shit!
該死!
三號芯片就緒
控制失敗!
Approaching rendezvous point.
接近交彙點
Dom! Tej and Roman are out! Where you at?
唐! 泰吉和羅曼都出局了! 你在哪?
I'm right behind you!
我就在你後方!
Stay on track. I'm taking the contingency.
你們接著開 我走應急車道
Boys, I got eyes on Shaw. He just made a left.
兄弟們 我看到肖了 他剛左轉了
- I got right.  - Toretto, make that left!
- 我跟著右路  - 托雷托 左轉!
薇戈
我需要你的幫忙
No problem.
沒問題
Letty.
萊蒂
Take the wheel.
你來開車
Letty.
萊蒂
This is crazy.
這太瘋狂了
We are not in Brazil.
我們可不是在巴西
So, now we got cars flying in the air?
我們真要搞的汽車滿天飛?
On some 007-type shit? This is not what we do.
就像007那樣? 這不是我們該幹的
Man, you really got to check that emotion.
兄弟 你真得控制下情緒了
Your voice just went from Shaggy to Scooby-Doo.
你說話都從一個大男人變成史酷比了
"This is not what we..."
"這不是我們..."
See, man, when a woman starts shooting at you,
聽著 夥計 如果一個女人朝你開槍
that's a clear sign to back the fuck off!
她就是想明確告訴你 讓你滾遠點!
We need to get the hell out of Dodge!
我們必須收手了!
That could have been my forehead, man.
今天撞塌的可能就是我的腦門 兄弟
No.
不會
That's not as big as your forehead.
這哪有你的腦門那麼大
Mia...
米婭...
Uh, It's definitely Letty.
呃 那肯定是萊蒂
But it's, uh... it's complicated.
但是 呃... 一言難盡啊
Letty's alive.
萊蒂還活著
That's all that matters.
這就足夠了
We have her back, Brian.
把她帶回來 布萊恩
Well, do me a favor and give Jack a kiss goodnight for me.
代我給傑克一個晚安吻
- Be safe.  - I love you, Mia.
- 注意安全  - 我愛你 米婭
She definitely saw it was you?
她看清楚了是你?
She looked dead at me, Brian.
她直直地盯著我 布萊恩
Maybe the Letty we once knew is gone, Dom.
或許我們曾經熟知的那個萊蒂已經不在了 唐
Even though she's alive, maybe she's gone.
就算她還活著 也可能已經不是那個她了
You don't turn your back on family.
就算家人背棄我們
Even when they do.
我們也不能背棄他們
- Ivory.  - Yo.
- 艾弗裏  - 在
It's going to need some repairs.
這車得修修了
No problem, treacle.
沒問題 甜心
Are you good?
你沒事兒吧?
Yeah.
沒事兒
Okay, listen up.
聽好了
That was a very different breed
那幫人可不是
from Hobbs' usual wannabe warriors.
霍布斯手下的小嘍囉
We need to learn who these people are, what they're made of.
咱們得知道他們是誰 有幾斤幾兩
Vegh?
薇戈?
O'Conner, Parker,
奧康納 帕克
Pearce, Toretto
皮爾斯 托雷托
and the rest of the team.
還有隊裏其他人
These guys are common criminals.
不過是些普通罪犯
Tonight these common criminals were seconds away
而今晚正是這些所謂的"普通罪犯"
from taking us down.
差一點就把我們拿下了
Show them the respect they deserve, or it weakens us.
給他們點顏色看看 不然倒黴的是我們
You might want to see this.
你可能會想看看這張
Ring any bells?
眼熟嗎?
Yeah.
是啊
That's the guy I shot.
就是我開槍打的那個
You look happy.
照片上你笑得很開心
I don't remember him.
我不記得這個人
That's bullshit.
胡說八道
We got a problem, guys.
這是個問題
We got a picture of her with the guy who almost took you out.
這兒有張她跟那個差點幹掉你的男人的照片
Klaus, aren't you team muscle?
克勞斯 你不是隊上的真爺們兒嗎?
Don't make me go over there and make you team pussy.
當心我過來把你弄成隊上的真娘們兒
She doesn't remember him.
她確實不記得他
Names and records aren't enough.
光有名字和檔案還不夠
I want personal information. Get into their lives, into their minds.
我要他們的個人信息 打入他們的生活 他們的心靈
Find their weaknesses, and we will exploit them.
找出他們的軟肋 為我們所用
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, right.
嗯哼 對了
This is crazy, man.
簡直瘋了
What are you talking about now?
你又想說什麼?
I'm sitting here looking at these images...
我坐在那兒看著那些照片...
It's like we're hunting our evil twins.
咱們的獵物簡直就像是自己的反派雙胞胎
Look at this black dude right here, he's handsome.
看看這邊這位黑人老兄 帥極了
Clearly, that's me.
明顯就是我
We got a white Hobbs. This is Han.
這兒有個白人版霍布斯 這個是韓
Tej, it's an African in a beanie.
泰吉 就是這個戴小帽兒的非洲人
That's like your Mini-Me, man.
就像你的微縮版
And Brian!
還有布萊恩!
When did you do this photo shoot?
你這張什麼時候拍的?
I'm just playing, man.
就開個玩笑 老兄
You know you're the prettiest blonde around here.
你知道你就是這兒最漂亮的金發妞兒了
All right, lock it up. We got two things.
好了 注意了 兩件事
First off, this is the worst damn city in the world to commit a crime.
第一 這兒是最不適合犯罪的一座城市
They got cameras on every street corner.
每個街角都布滿攝像頭
I got video footage from CCTV of the raid.
我拿到了突擊現場的監控錄像
Let's track that, see where it leads us.
咱們順藤摸瓜 看看有什麼收獲
And secondly, we just got confirmation
第二 我們剛剛確認了
on what Shaw's crew grabbed from Interpol.
肖的團隊從國際刑警那裏搶走了什麼
They ripped off the database
他們竊取了數據庫裏
of every location that houses the final component that they need.
記錄了他們所需最終零件存放點的列表
So where are they at?
那他們要去哪兒?
There are over two dozen of them around Europe.
遍布歐洲有超過12個存放點
But the list is only good for 96 hours.
但列表只有96小時的時效
Which means, wherever Shaw's crew is going to hit next,
也就意味著 無論肖的下一個目標是哪兒
it's going to happen within the next four days.
一定是未來四天之內的事
They got a window, and so do we.
他們有時間 我們也有
- We gotta move.  - Hobbs is right.
- 我們得開工了  - 霍布斯說得對
So let's break this down.
我們來分析一下情況
You met them. What do we know?
你們跟他們交過手 我們知道些什麼?
We know they have to be running custom engines.
他們用的肯定是訂制引擎
You heard that flip car going through those gears.
你聽到那輛飛車齒輪轉動的聲音
Sequential transmission.
是連續變速器
That didn't sound like a normal engine.
聽著不像是普通引擎
That was a turbo diesel.
是台渦輪柴油機
It sounded like something you hear at Le Mans.
聽著像是在勒芒賽道才會有的聲音
Did you see it take all those hits
你們有沒有注意到它經曆
and still stay flat in the corners?
那麼多次撞擊過彎依舊抓地很好?
Yeah, hydraulics.
是啊 液壓裝置
Or magnetic suspension.
也可能是磁浮裝置
Who not only has access to the components,
有誰既能搞到那些零件
but can fabricate something like that?
又能裝配出那麼一輛家夥?
Maybe a handful of shops in London.
可能是從倫敦的一堆商店裏
Regular tuner shops aren't going to cut it on this one.
一般的改裝店不會染指這玩意兒
We're going to have to dig deeper than that.
我們得再深入些挖掘
Han, Gisele, Roman, you're up.
韓 吉賽爾 羅曼 你們去
We find the guy who made that car,
一旦找到那個造車的人
we find Shaw.
我們就能找到肖
Let's go.
咱們走
- I'll help.  - Roger that.
- 我去幫忙  - 好的
Tej, we're gonna need cars without computer chips that can be overridden.
泰吉 我們需要不會被操控電腦芯片的車
Make sure they're fast.
確保它們迅如閃電
I got this.
包在我身上
I'm already on it, Dom. I've contacted R&D at DSS.
我已經著手在辦 唐 我跟外交安全局的研發部門聯系過了
Hobbs...
霍布斯...
I said I got this.
我說了包在我身上
This should be interesting.
肯定會很有趣的
Man, you really got to loosen up.
老兄 你真該想開點
You can't just throw a bunch of factory-line Beemers at people and expect...
你不能扔給我們一堆流水線上下來的寶馬車就指望...
Hey. That car is a hell of a car.
嘿 那可是輛好車
You're talking about twin-turbo V8,
那可是雙渦輪V8
spitting out 560 ponies, son.
輸出功率560馬的好車 小子
He reads the brochure. I'm proud.
居然讀了宣傳冊 我要自豪死了
But with cars, you have to customize.
但你必須改裝自己的車
It's all between you and the car you build.
這會在你跟你打造的座駕之間
It's a bond, it's a commitment.
形成一種紐帶 一種許諾
It sounds like a marriage.
聽著像婚姻
Yeah, but with cars, when you trade up,
是啊 可是對於車子 你賣次買好的時候
they don't take half your shit.
人家可不會卷走你一半的家當
Jesus.
天啊
With price tags like this, these cars better be made out of gold.
這麼高的價格 這車只能是金子造的
You ain't thinking about stealing these cars, are you, Parker?
帕克 你不會是想偷車吧?
Kitchen help entrance is towards the back.
廚房人員通道在後面
Come again?
你說什麼?
I don't mean any offense, gentlemen,
無意冒犯 兩位先生
but you couldn't possibly afford the cars in this auction.
不過這場拍賣會的車 你們絕對買不起任何一款
Substantial lack of gaudy jewelry, no entourage, no honeys.
嚴重缺乏華麗的珠寶 沒有隨從 沒有美人兒
Clearly you're not a "baller."
明顯你不是什麼"款爺"
And you.
還有你
Hmm. Shoes, shirt, trousers.
嗯 鞋子 襯衫 褲子
Functional.
實用
And your posture, too rigid, no swagger.
還有你的站姿 太僵硬 沒生氣
My guess is military. Take home of 50,000 a year.
我猜是軍隊的人 每年帶回家五萬
That's U.S.
還是美金
Which is not enough to be playing here.
不夠你們在這兒晃悠的
So, if you're not kitchen help,
所以 要是你們不是廚房助手
then you must be in the wrong place.
那你們一定是來錯地方了
But please, do finish your champagne.
不過請千萬喝完你們的香檳再走
Oh, he needs to be taught a lesson.
哦 那家夥實在是欠揍
Like I said, you ain't stealing these cars.
我還是那句話 你可不能偷車
I got this.
包在我身上
All right, this is number five on our list.
好了 這是名單上的第五個
Holy shit.
媽的
What's the dude plan on hunting? Moby Dick?
那家夥是要抓什麼玩意兒? 白鯨嗎?
That must be our guy.
肯定就是我們要找的人了
So, how do you all want to play this?
有什麼打算?
Han and I got this.
我跟韓來搞定
We go in tight, you let me do all the talking,
我們小心地進去 我來負責說
and you all have my back on it.
你們殿後
There's one thing you boys are forgetting.
你們忽略了一點
He's a man.
他是個男人
Let's go.
咱們走
"He's a man"?
"他是個男人"?
You know, she always says that.
她一直這麼說的
What you're looking at is a 5.45 by 18 FMJ spitzer bullet.
這是顆5.45乘18的全金屬披甲彈
It's specific to one handgun, the PSM.
是PSM手槍的專用子彈
Given that handguns are illegal in the United Kingdom,
鑒於這種手槍在英國是非法的
there's very few people that have access to that firearm.
能弄到這種武器的人極少
So if somebody wanted to, say,
所以要是你想讓人
track down where it came from,
摸清這槍從哪兒來的
it wouldn't be too hard.
也不會太難的
I was a cop for a lot of years. Some habits die hard.
我當了很多年警察 有些習慣改不了
A pawn shop.
是間當鋪
Who sent you?
誰派你們來的?
Come on, ladies!
美女們!
Two hot girls like you don't wander into this neighborhood
除非我叫了特殊服務 否則不可能
unless I've called the escort service.
有兩個火辣妹子來我這閑逛的
And I haven't, yet, today.
今天我還沒叫呢
I don't know, man. That was disrespectful.
我不明白 這不太高雅
And I don't like the way she said it,
我也不喜歡她說的
like, "He's a man."
"他是個男人"
"He's a man"? So, what are we?
"他是個男人"? 那我們是什麼?
Come on, she's just doing her job.
算了 她在工作而已
"Doing her job."
"工作"啊
I see what's going on.
我知道怎麼回事了
See what?
知道什麼?
You got the little stardust in your eyes, eh?
你心裏有點小不爽 是吧?
Little birds floating around a little bit.
頭腦發暈 小鳥盤旋
Uh, you don't want to lease this model. You want to buy.
你不是想租她 是想買吧
Can you please stop talking?
能別再說了嗎?
No, no, you're in love! Look at you!
不 你愛上她了! 瞧瞧你!
Just stop.
別說了
You got special plans? Big day?
你有計劃嗎? 結婚?
You're going to invite us all out?
你會邀請我們嗎?
Better make sure you get her a big rock, man,
你一定要給她個大鑽戒 朋友
'cause she doesn't look like she'll be that easily impressed.
她看上去不會輕易被打動
And if it's not a big rock,
如果沒有大鑽戒
you better be big somewhere else.
其它地方大也行啊
You know what I'm talking about.
你知道我說的是什麼
That's why all your girlfriends wear so much bling, huh?
怪不得你女朋友都穿金戴銀的
We're looking for information.
我們需要情報
You're looking for information? About what?
你們要情報? 什麼情報?
Information about cars.
關於車的
In particular, two you designed recently.
特別是最近你設計的兩款
Ramp cars. Low slung, skeletal frames.
爬坡狠 底盤低 結構小巧
We'd be very interested to find the man who bought those.
我們很想找到這車的買家
Why should I help you?
我為什麼要幫你們?
Because we're asking you nicely.
因為我們態度良好
Because you're asking me nicely?
態度良好?
What can you offer that I can't get from a thousand other girls?
你們能提供什麼其他女孩提供不了的嗎?
Hmm?
嗯?
Stop! Stop!
停下! 停下!
You look like a man who likes it rough.
你好像喜歡被折磨
My friend here can give you heights of pain
我朋友可以給你帶來痛苦的巔峰
you've never experienced before.
是你從沒有經曆過的
Do we have a deal?
我們說好了?
Deal! Deal! Deal!
成交! 成交! 成交!
I take it back.
我收回那句話
Me likey.
我也喜歡這妞
Stop, stop, stop.
停停停
So this is how you "got this"? By buying all of his cars?
所以這就是你所謂的方法? 買下他所有的車?
What good is having millions of dollars in the bank
百萬存款在銀行裏卻不花
if you don't spend any of it?
有什麼用?
But don't worry about that. Watch this.
別擔心 看著
Mr. Parker, again, can I just express our gratitude
帕克先生 請容許我再次表達感謝之意
and say how much we appreciate your business.
謝謝您的惠顧
If there's ever anything else you need, you just have to ask.
如果還有任何什麼需要 請盡管開口
- Anything?  - Mmm-hmm.
- 任何需要?  - 沒錯
Now that you mention it, my swagger-less friend here,
既然你提到了 我這位不喜浮誇的朋友
he really likes that shirt you have on.
很喜歡你身上的襯衫
Uh, this shirt?
這件嗎?
That shirt.
是的
I'm not entirely sure that this shirt would fit your friend.
這襯衫你的朋友恐怕穿不下
It will fit.
穿得下
He needs a shirt that's a little less...
他需要一件襯衫不那麼...
Functional.
實用的
That's it, functional.
就這個詞 實用的
Okay.
好吧
- I'll hold that.  - Thank you.
- 我拿著吧  - 謝謝
Come on, man, time is money.
快點 時間就是金錢
Yes, doing my best.
好的 我盡快
Damn, you need some hedge clippers for that shit.
天啊 你需要修剪一下胸毛了
Well, if that will be all...
如果沒什麼需要...
And the pants, too.
還有褲子
Right.
好的
While you're at it, let me get that watch.
既然這樣 我要那塊表
I like that watch.
我喜歡那塊表
This is for you.
這是給你的
- And this is for you.  - Thank you.
- 這是給你的  - 謝謝
Good day, gentlemen. Thank you.
玩得開心 先生們 謝謝
So I, um,
那麼 呃
I got the information in here.
我把資料都放這裏
May I ask why you're looking for Shaw?
我能問你們為什麼要找肖嗎?
He took something of ours.
他抓走了我們的人
We'd like to talk to him about it.
我們想和他談談
Let's see what we've got.
我們看看都有什麼
All right. What do you want?
好吧 你要什麼?
They say if someone's looking for a Russian gun,
有人說想要俄羅斯的槍
you're the man to see.
就來你這
Oh, they do, do they?
哦 有人說啊?
What do you want, mate?
你要什麼 夥計?
That might be a bad idea.
不想死就別進來
- I'm looking for the owner of this.  - I don't know.
- 我在找它的主人  - 我不知道
Take a closer look.
看仔細點
About a week ago, a girl came in,
一周前 一個女孩來
bought guns, ammo, everything I had.
買了所有的槍和武器
A girl?
女孩?
What did she look like?
她長什麼樣?
Tough cheek, dark hair.
瘦削的臉頰 黑發
Mean streak.
身材苗條
Word is she's a street racer.
有人說她是賽車手
Where can we find her?
我們去哪找她?
How do I know? Do I look like a racer?
我怎麼知道? 我像是賽車手嗎?
No. You don't.
不 你不像
Take care, guys.
保重
Oh, shit.
不妙
Sorry, girls.
抱歉 美女
Let's go!
我們走!
Hold on.
挺住
Stay with me. Stay with me.
看著我 看著我
Tell me where to find Shaw,
告訴我去哪找肖
and I'll make him pay for this.
我為你報仇
Braga...
布拉加...
Ow!
啊!
Hey, you!
嘿 你!
Stop right there!
站住別動!
- You go!  - No, you go!
- 你上!  - 不 你上!
No one needs to know about this.
這事兒不能讓別人知道
No one.
不能
We lost Ivory.
我們失去了艾弗裏
He's gone.
他死了
Thanks.
謝謝
That's it?
就這樣?
If Ivory's dead, he made a mistake.
他犯錯了 所以才會死
If you make a mistake, you pay the price.
如果你犯錯了 你也得付出代價
That's a great eulogy, Shaw.
至理名言啊 肖
Are you going to give the same speech
是不是我們死的時候
for the rest of us when we go out?
你也會說同樣的話?
You're the last one I'd have pegged to be sentimental.
你是唯一一個會讓我感情用事的人
I like you, Letty.
我喜歡你 萊蒂
I dare say I even feel a certain warmth towards you.
我敢說我甚至感到了溫暖
When I found you in the hospital,
當我在醫院裏找到你
and you couldn't remember anything,
你不記得所有事
I said to myself,
我對自己說
"This girl has a gift."
"這女孩有天賦"
"She's a blank page."
"她是一張白紙"
And that made me feel somewhat protective toward you.
這激起了我對你的保護欲
If something happened to you, for instance,
如果你發生什麼意外
I think I might find that slightly harder to bear.
我會比較難接受的
What I'm saying is,
我是說
I would hate to see you
我不希望你
make a mistake.
犯錯
I'm going to get some air.
我出去透透氣
- What the hell happened?  - We met Dom's girlfriend.
- 出了什麼事?  - 我們遇到了唐的女朋友
She's lovely.
她很可愛
- Are you all right?  - Yeah.
- 你還好嗎?  - 還好
Tej, what have you got? Footage, CCTV? Talk to me.
泰吉 你從監控中發現什麼了? 告訴我
I just went through all of it.
我剛看完所有的監控錄像
Believe it or not, everywhere Shaw's team is, the cameras are down.
只要是肖的手下出現的地方 監控像頭就壞了
That's a hell of a coincidence.
真是巧合啊
All right, we're going to pay CCTV a little visit. Let's roll.
我們得去趟監控中心 走吧
What is that?
那是什麼?
That is a new toy for you.
給你的新玩具
So, what happened?
除了什麼事?
Shaw's goons showed up and started shooting up the place.
肖的手下一來就射穿了那地方
But we got something big.
但我們有重大線索
- What?  - Braga.
- 什麼?  - 布拉加
He's working with Shaw.
他和肖合作了
What are you talking about?
你說什麼?
It's true. That phone's filled with coded payment transactions
是真的 電話裏都是加密的交易信息
that lead straight to Braga's cartel.
所有信息都指向布拉加
Who the hell is Braga?
布拉加是誰?
He ran one of the biggest cartels in Mexico.
他在墨西哥有聯合企業
And my old boss.
是我上任老板
We used codes just like that
以前我們就用密碼
to move money out of the country.
把錢轉移到國外
It all makes sense.
這就很清楚了
Braga was running Letty, now he's working with Shaw.
布拉加過去讓萊蒂運過車 現在他和肖合作
It would explain how the two of them met.
這就說明了他們怎麼會在一起
Okay, so you all know all this information
好吧 現在你們知道了他的所有信息
about him, where do we find him?
去哪兒找他?
He's sitting in a prison in Los Angeles.
他在洛杉磯監獄
How do you know that?
你怎麼知道?
Brian put him there.
布萊恩把他弄進去的
All right, so this is the break we were looking for.
好吧 這就是我們一直在找的突破口
If the two of them were working together,
如果他倆是一丘之貉
Braga will know what Shaw's up to.
布拉加就知道肖在哪
I'm going to pay him a visit.
我要進去見見他
Are you serious right now?
你說真的?
Think about what you're saying.
聽聽你自己在說什麼
You're wanted, Brian.
你被通緝了 布萊恩
The moment you step foot off that plane, it's a wrap.
你一下飛機就完蛋了
You're not coming back.
你可能回不來的
"Coming back"? How are you going to get in the country?
"回來"? 你要怎麼進入美國國境?
Let me worry about that.
這事我來操心
This is on me.
這是我的錯
I'm the one that served her up to Braga.
是我把她推給布拉加的
I'm the one that gets to make it right.
我要挽回這一切
Let me make it right.
讓我去吧
Be careful.
小心點兒
He's ready to see you now. Right this way.
你們可以進來了 這邊請
Thank you for seeing us. I won't take up much of your time.
謝謝你見我們 不會耽誤你太久
My men were attacked earlier today.
今天早晨我的人被攻擊了
I'm going to need to see all cameras
我要看下
in and around Waterloo station.
滑鐵盧站點的監控錄像
Will somebody tell Captain America here
誰來跟這位美國警官說說
that requires clearance?
查看監控是需要權限的?
Terry.
泰瑞
Bring up cameras 58 through 62, earlier today.
打開今天早晨58到62號的監控錄像
They've been down for maintenance all morning.
早晨這些攝像頭都在維護 沒有工作
Sorry.
不好意思
Okay. Well, we appreciate your help. Thank you.
哦 好吧 謝謝你的幫助 謝謝
You know what I find very interesting
你知道嗎? 我發現了一些有趣的事兒
is Interpol was attacked recently as well.
最近國際刑警組織也遭到攻擊
Those cameras were down, too. Didn't catch a thing.
監控攝像頭也壞了 沒有錄下任何東西
Nothing.
什麼都沒有
Now, that means either one of two things.
這說明兩件事情
Either means that your maintenance schedule here
要麼說明你們的維護系統
aligns perfectly with their escape route
跟他們的逃跑路線完全一致
or it means that someone here is working with them.
要麼說明你們這裏有內鬼
And that's just ridiculous.
這就太可笑了
Because there ain't no way in hell
因為這裏的人絕對不可能
anybody here would be working for them.
會為他們賣命的
Particularly you, ain't that right?
尤其是你 我說得對嗎?
No, no, that's ridiculous.
不 這不可能
That is ridiculous.
不可能
I'm going to need direct access to your live feed
我要直接進入你們全市直播監控錄像的
citywide.
權限
And I also strongly suggest that you put a hold on any more
我強烈建議不要再
"maintenance."
"維護"了
Yeah, of course.
是 當然
We appreciate your help. Thank you so much.
感謝你的協助 非常感謝
洛杉磯
Well, well, well.
看看 看看
The orange in that really makes your eyes pop.
你穿著這衣服真是讓人眼前一亮
Thanks, fellas.
謝謝 老兄
Tell me something, O'Conner,
來 告訴我 奧康納
how is it you keep running around the world,
你是怎麼擺脫人類的法律
breaking every law known to man,
浪跡天涯
and yet here I am, putting my job on the line for you?
然後又落到了我手裏的?
You'll feel a lot better once you get the credit for taking down Shaw.
如果抓到肖的功勞算在你頭上 你感覺會好很多
Oh, I'm tempted to settle for you.
能逮捕你 我就很開心
Well, you know what they say, Stasiak,
好吧 你知道他們都怎麼說嗎? 斯塔希亞克
if you want the career-changing big fish,
如果你想釣上改變一切的大魚
you got to be willing to put on the big boy panties
就得穿上潛水服
and sail out to the deep water.
潛入更深的水底
You're an asshole, you know that'?
你個混蛋 你知道嗎?
I missed you, too, man. I really missed you.
我也很想你啊 老兄 我真的很想你
I got you admitted into Victorville to do whatever you got to do.
幫你批准了進入勝利穀去做你應該做的
It's a 24-hour hold.
你只有24小時
You need to be out of there by 9:00 a.m.
你必須在上午9點前出來
That's when Forensics will run your fingerprints through the national database.
到時取證人員會通過國際數據庫錄入你的指紋
That program will match you
等程序裏搜到和你溫和的指紋
and when they find out who you really are,
發現你的真實身份之後
I won't be able to get you back out.
就沒辦法撈你出來了
We're talking life in prison.
以後我們就要在監獄裏面聊天了
Cute kid.
很可愛的孩子
So, I found out Braga's being held in cell block D3.
那麼 我已經查到布拉加關在D3牢房
That's solitary.
那是單人牢房
I only had enough juice to get you in Gen Pop.
我只能幫你安排進普通牢房
So you're going to have to do something to get his attention.
那麼你就做些事情引起他的注意吧
Sorry about this, man.
對不起了 老兄
Sorry about what?
對不起什麼?
Again?
又來?
Big Brother's about to go live.
現場直播開始了
Damn, you can't flick a booger in London without somebody noticing.
該死 在倫敦挖鼻屎都能被人看見
Hey! Don't touch that. That's nothing to play with, man.
嘿! 別碰那個 那不是什麼玩具 老兄
What's the problem?
怎麼了?
That's high-tensile titanium cable.
這是氣鈦電纜
What does that mean?
什麼意思?
That's what they use to anchor buildings and hold up bridges,
是用來射在建築或者橋梁上的
stuff you know nothing about!
你不懂這玩意兒!
See, now, their version, it works cool,
好吧 換個說法 就是它們很拉風
but mine, masterpiece.
我打造的更是絕無僅有
See, I reversed the gears, torqued the motor
看 我調換了齒輪 調整了發動機
and added this tank to the back.
在尾部加上了這個氣缸
That makes it even sweeter.
讓這武器更厲害了
It does.
的確是
It's not dummy-proof.
這不是山寨貨
Man, I've been known to handle big guns. Relax.
兄弟 我玩兒過更大的槍 放松
You've been known to handle that big-ass head.
你以前玩兒的是大頭槍
Dom, I did some checking, asked around,
唐 我四處打聽了一下
got the location of a street race tonight.
弄到了今晚賽車的地方
Four speed Camaro SS big block.
這車是四速大黃蜂
You like it?
怎麼樣?
Nice color.
顏色不錯
Brian O'Conner.
布萊恩·奧康納
That was quite an entrance.
你的入獄可真是精彩
You put a lot of these men in here.
這裏有很多人是你抓進來的
What? You didn't think one would recognize you?
怎麼? 你認為沒人能夠認出你?
I've kept tabs on you, you know.
要知道 我已經盯了你很久了
You've been having a lot of fun out there.
你在外面很逍遙啊
Good cop gone bad, Rio de Janeiro.
裏約熱內盧 好警察變節
It's exciting when you go criminal, isn't it?
你犯事兒的時候很興奮 是吧?
Too bad you didn't do it earlier, you could have worked for me.
太遺憾了 你沒有早點兒犯事兒 你本來可以為我工作的
Like Letty Ortiz?
就像萊蒂·奧提茲?
So tell me something, because I buried her.
所以告訴我點事情 畢竟是我埋了她
Yeah? You did?
是嗎? 你埋的?
You buried something, I couldn't tell you who or what it was.
你的確埋了東西 但我不能告訴你究竟埋下去了什麼
I know she's running with Owen Shaw.
我知道她現在和歐文·肖在一起
Still playing cop, huh?
還在扮演警察的角色 是嗎?
Trust me, this is way above your pay grade.
相信我 這不是你這級別的人該知道的
Humor me, please.
說說看
Well, you're a dead man walking, what does it matter'?
好吧 反正你也死定了 告訴你又有何妨?
I ran everything for Shaw.
我幫肖做很多事兒
Drugs, guns, money, women.
販毒 販槍 洗錢 找女人
He taught me to think global when I was just local.
當我還是個草根時 是他教會我目光遠大
He made me a wealthy man.
是他讓我變得富有
And this guy didn't just have the cartels working for him.
他不僅有聯合企業
He had the CIA, DEA, everyone in his pocket.
中情局 毒品稽查局都受他擺布
He knew what was going to happen before they did.
他能在事前就知道他們的行動
In fact, he even knew when some wet-behind-the-ears FBI agent
實際上 他甚至知道聯邦調查局什麼時候
decided to put some informant in my cartel.
在我的公司安插的線人
The minute you put Letty undercover, she was dead, bro.
你安排萊蒂做臥底的時候 她就已經死定了 老兄
But she survived.
但是她還活著
That girl is one tough bitch.
她真是個十足的婊子
Shaw found her in a hospital two days later.
兩天後 肖在醫院發現了她
He went to finish the job.
他是去解決她的
And he didn't kill her. Why?
但卻沒有動手 為什麼?
She had no memory.
因為她失去了記憶
Perfect girl, huh?
真是完美 是吧?
You're lucky this door's between us.
你該慶幸還有這扇門擋著我
What happened to Letty is on your head.
萊蒂的遭遇都是你的錯
Look at me! Look at me.
看著我! 看著我
You won't do it.
你不會殺我的
What is Shaw up to?
肖有什麼計劃?
How do you think he knows your next move before you make it?
你認為他是怎麼知道你們下一步計劃的?
He's got eyes on you.
他已經在你們周圍安插了線人
Think about it.
仔細想想
The only way you get close to Shaw
唯一能接近肖的辦法
is if he wants you there.
就是他想讓你接近他
You've got some serious balls, man.
你的確夠有膽量
I've been told.
是有人這麼說過
You know, you're lucky I missed my shot.
你該慶幸我上次打偏了
I think you hit your mark.
我覺得你打中了
Really?
是嗎?
What is it with you?
你到底想幹什麼?
Do you got a death wish or something?
想找死還是怎樣?
If that's what it takes，
哪怕結局是一死
I just want to race.
我還是想賽車
You might lose your car.
你可能會輸掉你的車
Let's do it.
比了才知道
Your funeral.
你死定了
Ride or die, remember?
拼死一搏 還記得嗎?
Listen up!
聽著!
Out here, we're used to getting what we want.
在這裏我們總是能得到我們想要的
This is London, baby.
這裏可是倫敦 寶貝
But remember,
但記住了
don't bite the bait.
千萬別被誘惑了
Are you ready?
你們准備好了嗎?
- Ready?  - Ready.
- 准備好了嗎?  - 准備好了
Steady.
預備
Go!
開始!
Just like old times.
簡直跟以前一樣
This guy is crazy.
這個人瘋了吧
You got to be kidding me.
跟我開玩笑呢
You're still upshifting early.
你換擋還是太早了
I do that so you brake.
我這麼做你才會刹車
You lose traction and the back end kicks out.
這樣車尾就會打滑
I noticed.
我注意到了
Look, just because you know how I ride, doesn't mean you know me.
雖然你知道我開車的習慣 並不代表你了解我
You know what they say where we're from?
你知道我們那個地方的人怎麼說嗎?
Show me how you drive, I'll show you who you are.
讓我看看你是怎麼開車的 我就能知道你是怎樣的人
V8.
V8發動機
You never could resist American muscle.
你永遠也拒絕不了美國肌肉車
Nice scar.
好漂亮的疤
You never could keep yourself out of trouble, either.
你還是一直在給自己找麻煩
What else do you know about me?
你還知道我的什麼事情?
About you?
關於你?
Everything.
所有的一切
Like this scar.
比如這條疤
You got that the first night we met. You were 15.
這是我們第一次見面的那個晚上留下的 你那時15歲
First street race.
第一次公路賽車
Some kid trying to show off lost control of his car,
有個小孩想炫耀下車技 結果失控了
wiped out right next to you.
車就在你旁邊撞毀
You're lucky you didn't lose your arm.
你很幸運你沒有失去一條手臂
And let me guess,
讓我猜猜看
you saved me.
你救了我
No.
不是
I was the kid showing off.
我是那個炫耀的小孩
And here...
還有這裏...
Boyle Heights.
博爾高地
You were fleeing with my little sister Mia and got trapped in a corner.
你和我妹妹米婭一起逃跑 結果被困在角落裏
And you thought it was a good idea
你以為
to ride your Torino Cobra through a retaining wall.
開著都靈響尾蛇穿牆而過是個好主意
All right, how about this one?
好吧 那這個呢?
That's the last time we were together.
這是我們在一起的最後一個晚上留下的
In the DR,
在裏約的時候
you wanted to go for a night swim.
你想晚上去遊泳
You cut yourself on the reef.
結果被暗礁劃傷了
I followed you.
我跟著你
I even got this scar to match.
我甚至也劃了條一模一樣的疤
Look, I don't know why you're here,
我不知道你為什麼在這裏
but I really think you're over your head.
但我真的覺得你腦袋不清醒
I'm here for you.
我是為了你來的
That girl you remember,
你記憶中的那個姑娘
it's not me.
不是我
Not from what I just saw.
我剛剛看到的不是這樣
Like it or not,
不管你喜不喜歡
you're still the same girl.
你一點沒變
I saw it out there.
我之前就知道
I see it right now.
我現在更確信了
I got to go.
我得走了
Hey
等一下
It belongs to you.
這是你的
There she goes,
她走了
leaving you again.
又一次離開你了
Bloody fickle, that one.
這姑娘真絕情啊
You want bloody? We could do bloody.
你想來狠的? 我可以奉陪
A street kid,
一個街頭小混混
starts out stealing DVD players in East L.A.,
在洛杉磯東部偷DVD播放機
ends up heisting $100 million in Rio.
最後卻在裏約搶了一個億
Not bad, huh?
不錯吧?
It's a good story, isn't it?
是個好故事 不是嗎?
Almost inspiring.
還很勵志
See, what I couldn't fathom is
但我不能理解的是
why he's not relaxing on a beach somewhere
他為什麼不和那個漂亮的巴西小妞
with that cute little Brazilian number.
待在沙灘上放松放松
Instead, he's working with a two-bit government hack like Hobbs.
卻要和政府走狗霍布斯在一起
And then I realized,
然後我意識到
he has a weak spot.
他有一個弱點
We all got a weak spot.
我們大家都有弱點
You know,
聽我說
when I was young, my brother always used to say,
在我小時候 我哥哥總是說
"Every man has to have a code."
"每個人都有原則"
Mine?
我的?
Precision.
縝密
A team is nothing but pieces you switch out until you get the job done.
所謂的團隊只是為了達成任務而組合到一起的零件
It's efficient.
高效
It works.
而且實用
But you?
但是你呢?
You're loyal to a fault.
你對錯誤的想法忠貞不渝
Your code is about family.
你的原則和家人有關
And that's great in the holidays, but it makes you predictable.
過節的時候有家人還不錯 但它讓你的行動很容易被預料
And in our line of work, predictable means vulnerable.
幹我們這行的 這意味著脆弱
And that means I can reach out and break you whenever I want.
也就是說 只要我想 我就可以找到你並且打敗你
At least when I go, I'll know what it's for.
至少在我死的時候 我知道我是為什麼而死的
Well,
好吧
at least you have a code.
至少你還有原則
Most men don't.
大多數人沒有
So,
那麼
I'm going to give you a chance.
我給你一次機會
Take your crew and walk away.
帶著你的人離開這兒
That's the only way you're going to keep your family safe.
這是保護你家人安全的唯一辦法
Your brother never told you never to threaten a man's family?
你哥哥難道沒有告訴過你 永遠別拿家人去威脅別人嗎?
It's a pretty stupid thing to do.
這非常愚蠢
But I'll make it simple for you.
但事情也可以變得很簡單
I walk away when she walks away.
放了她 我就走
Well, then,
好吧
it appears this inspiring tale has come to an end.
看來這個勵志故事要結束了
If that's the way it has to go.
如果一定要這樣的話
Let me guess...
讓我猜猜...
Hobbs.
是霍布斯吧
Come on, you son of a bitch.
來吧 狗娘養的
The "two-bit government hack."
那個"政府走狗"
See you around, Toretto.
回頭見 托雷托
You can bet on it.
一定會再見的
Riley, Shaw's leaving Battersea, heading southeast.
萊麗 肖離開巴特西朝東南方向走了
Have Tej track him on his live feed. Go.
讓泰吉在實時監控裏追蹤他 快
You know what would have happened
要知道 如果我沒有把跟蹤器放在你車裏
if I didn't put that tracker in your car?
會發生什麼嗎?
This one?
這個嗎?
You know, this just got me one step closer to Shaw.
它讓我離肖更近了一步
For what it's worth, Toretto,
不管怎樣 托雷托
I hope it gets you closer to what you want, too.
我希望你也能早點得到你想要的
This better have been worth it.
這麼做最好值得
More than you'll ever know.
太值得了
Pretty.
美女
May I?
我可以看看嗎?
I'm going to ask you a question, Letty,
我想要問你一個問題 萊蒂
and I want you to think very hard before you answer.
而且我希望你在回答我之前仔細考慮清楚
When I give you the order
如果我命令你
to take Toretto out,
去殺掉托雷托
what will your first thought be?
你的第一反應是什麼?
Why don't you look me in the eye
你為什麼不看著我的眼睛
and you tell me what you see.
告訴我你看到了什麼
Keep it.
你留著吧
Tej, talk to me, what have we got?
泰吉 說說看 情況如何了?
We were able to track Shaw after he left you and Dom,
肖離開你和唐之後 我們還可以追蹤到他
but this guy's smart, so we could only track him so far.
但這個家夥太聰明了 我們只能追蹤到這裏
He seems to know all the city's blind spots.
他好像知道這個城市裏所有的盲區
See, we lost him somewhere in here,
看 他就是在這裏附近消失的
which means he could be anywhere
也就是說他可能
within that half-a-mile radius.
在方圓半英裏的任何一個地方
Maybe if we cross-reference phone records, leases...
也許我們可以參照通話記錄 租約...
No, this has got Shaw's name written all over it.
不用了 這裏肯定就是肖的藏身點
We've got vantage points, multiple exits,
這裏有隱蔽點 出口
subways, highways and storm drains.
地鐵 高速路和下水道
Bad-ass and brains.
真傷腦筋
Woman, you keep that up, I'm going to be out of a job.
姑娘 你要再幹得這麼漂亮 我就要丟掉工作了
All right, let's go nail that son of a bitch.
好吧 我們去抓那個混蛋
They're long gone.
他們早走了
There's nothing here.
這兒什麼都沒有
There's never nothing.
不會什麼都沒有的
There's always something.
總會有些東西
Let's go, guys.
走吧 夥計們
Shaw, everyone is in place. All things moving according to plan.
肖 大家都就位了 一切按計劃進行
Good. Send him in.
好 派他進去
Yo, it's Hobbs.
呦 是霍布斯
What have you got, Parker? Give me something good.
你有什麼收獲 帕克? 告訴我些好消息
Yeah, that paint you got from Shaw's place is highly specialized.
好 你從肖那裏拿到是高度專業化的塗料
Anti-thermal low-IR coating.
抗熱低紅外線塗料
- Military.  - Exactly.
- 軍用的  - 沒錯
We got a list of bases around Europe that use this paint type
我們拿到了在歐洲使用這種油漆的基地清單
and those specific colors.
還有具體的顏色
All right, let's cross-reference that
好的 我們把它和肖的
with all of Shaw's military targets.
軍事目標進行對照
I guaran-damn-tee you one of them is gonna match.
我保證肯定有一個能對上
Bingo. It's a NATO base in Spain.
沒錯 是一個西班牙的北約基地
That puts Shaw in a different country.
照這麼說 肖就在另一個國家了
That means he's got an eight-hour lead on us.
也就意味著他比我們超前八個小時
We gotta move now. Tej, give me that info.
我們要走了 泰吉 把具體情況發給我
Riley and I will go ahead and we're going to lock down the base.
萊麗和我先過去 封鎖整個基地
We're going to protect that component personally.
我們將親自保護那個部件
Toretto, I'll arrange transportation for you and your cars.
托雷托 我會安排人把你們和車都帶過去
You brush up on your Spanish, boys. I'll see you en Espana.
你們溫習下西班牙語 夥計們 我們西班牙見
西班牙 路西塔尼亞 北約基地
You son of a bitch! You made it!
你個混蛋! 你成功了!
What up, man? Good to see you.
怎麼樣 哥們? 見到你真好
Good to see you. So, what's going on here?
見到你們真好 這裏怎麼了?
Figured out they're hitting an army base in Spain.
已經查出他們打算襲擊西班牙的一個軍事基地
Border patrol lD'ed Shaw's men crossing through last night.
昨晚海岸巡邏隊發現肖的人入境
Hobbs and Riley went to lock down the base.
霍布斯和萊麗已經去封鎖基地
- They're going to meet us there.  - Where's Dom?
- 他們會在那見我們  - 唐在哪?
He wasn't going without you.
沒有你他是不會走的
I found out what happened to Letty.
我知道了萊蒂到底出了什麼事
It's all my fault.
這都是我的錯
Brian,
布萊恩
whatever you found out, that's for you.
不管你發現了什麼 都是你的事
What we're about to do now
我們現在要做的事情
is for her.
是為了她
We've got four teams on overwatch,
我們有四隊人看守
sniper-spotters in roosts north and south of the target.
狙擊火力點分別在棲息點以北和目標以南
Just keep all your men out of sight.
只要你們的人別出現就好
When they drive that truck in here,
當他們把貨車開進來
I want to come crashing down on them like the walls of Jericho.
我會像耶利哥牆一樣粉碎他們
Hobbs, I just caught this one disabling the perimeter security system.
霍布斯 這個人企圖破壞周邊的安全防範系統 剛好被我逮到了
- Your house is compromised.  - What are you suggesting?
- 你方已經有人妥協了  - 你在暗示什麼?
I ain't suggesting.
我這不是暗示
We follow protocol, we move the component out.
我們遵守協定 把部件運出去
Shaw thinks it's here. We're going to get it out of here before he arrives.
肖認為它在這 我們要在他到之前把它運走
Stealth and speed are going to be our two best friends.
最好既悄無聲息又十分迅速
We're going to protect our little egg, move it out of the henhouse,
我們要保護我們的小雞蛋 把它移出雞窩
then we're going to wait for that goddamn fox to arrive.
然後就等著那該死的狐狸來
I just got word they caught one of Shaw's men at the base.
我剛得到消息 他們在基地抓到一個肖的人
It's time.
是時候了
Something is not right. He wanted us to find that guy.
有些不對勁 他故意讓我們找到那個人的
Think about it. At Interpol, you were face-to-face with him.
想想吧 在國際刑警總部 你和他正面交鋒過
Brian, so what are you saying?
布萊恩 那你的意思是?
Braga said the only way you get near Shaw is if he wants you to.
布拉加說接近肖的唯一辦法就是他想你靠近
Tej, where's that component?
泰吉 那個部件在哪?
They're moving it to a secure location.
他們正把它送到安全的地方
Shaw ain't hitting that base.
肖沒有打算襲擊基地
He's hitting the convoy.
他要襲擊護衛隊
Let's go!
我們走吧!
We've got a report, the convoy's under attack.
我們收到報告 護衛隊遭到襲擊
Get a chopper, now!
找架直升機 快!
Fellas, you better hurry up. They just took the convoy.
夥計們 你們得趕緊 他們剛襲擊了護衛隊
And Dom,
還有 唐
Letty's with them.
萊蒂和他們在一起
We stick to the plan.
我們執行原計劃
All right, you heard the man.
好吧 你聽到他的話了
Let's play this fast and clean.
快速利索地解決吧
That thing's heading your way.
它朝你開過來了
All systems go.
系統已准備好
Everything looks stable.
看起來一切都穩定
Uh, guys, we gotta come up with another plan.
呃 夥計們 我們得想另一個計劃
They got a tank.
他們有坦克
I'm sorry, did somebody just say "a tank"?
對不起 剛才有人說了"坦克"嗎?
We got company, guys.
有人來了 夥計們
Toretto is coming right at you.
托雷托正往你那去
Okay. Get the weapons hot.
好 准備武器
Give me satellite imaging.
給我衛星影像
Straight ahead of us.
在我們正前方
There you are.
你們在這啊
Who's got a plan B?
有沒有B計劃啊?
Plan B? We need a plan C, D, E.
B計劃? 我們需要C計劃 D計劃 E計劃
We need more alphabets!
我們還需要更多計劃!
Hey, we do what we do best.
嘿 做我們最擅長的事
We improvise, all right?
我們即興發揮 好吧?
Okay, Jah. Take it to the other side.
好吧 賈 把它開到對面車道
Let's have some fun.
我們玩一玩
What the hell is wrong with you? This isn't part of the plan.
你搞什麼? 計劃裏可沒這些
Take their attention away from the people!
把他們注意力從人群中移開!
Shaw, you don't have to do this.
肖 你不需要這麼做
We got one right in front of us.
我們正前方有一個
Boom.
砰
Oh, shit!
靠!
You lucky bastard.
你這走狗屎運的混蛋
Roman, you hang in there.
羅曼 你堅持住
Hang in there, man!
堅持住 兄弟!
Somebody better do something! I got a tank on my ass!
你們倒是做點什麼啊! 坦克就在我屁股後面!
There's gotta be a break up ahead.
前面的隔離帶肯定有缺口
Oh, look,
看
a bridge.
有座橋
Screw it.
好吧
Yeah!
耶!
We're dragging a car behind us.
我們後面拖了輛車
Brian, that Mustang would make a nice anchor.
布萊恩 那輛野馬可以當一個很好的錨
Yeah, I'm on it.
號 我知道了
Damn!
該死的!
Shaw, we've got to get rid of that car.
肖 我們必須擺脫那車
Letty, go take care of the cable.
萊蒂 去解開纜繩
Yeah!
耶!
What's she doing?
她在幹嘛?
Shit!
該死!
Okay, Toretto.
好 托雷托
Here's your girl...
這是你的女人...
and your happy ending.
和你們的完美結局
Letty!
萊蒂!
Jesus Christ.
天啊
I can't believe they stole a 70-ton tank
我不敢相信他們竟然為了個三盎司的電腦芯片
for a three-ounce computer chip.
偷一輛70噸重的坦克
That 3-ounce computer chip is more deadly than 1,000 of those tanks.
那三盎司的電腦芯片可比一千輛坦克致命多了
What about her?
她要怎麼處理呢?
Not her.
別打她的主意
She was working with Shaw.
她和肖一起做事
Was,
是曾經
but she's always been one of us.
但她一直都是我們的一員
Let's give them a minute.
給他們點時間
Let's go process Shaw and his crew.
我們來處理肖和他的手下
I've never looked more forward to filling out paperwork in my life.
我從沒像現在這樣這麼期待填文件
Hey.
嘿
Look, I don't even know how to say this to you,
我甚至不知道怎麼和你說
but everything that's happened here is because of me.
但這裏發生的所有事情都是因為我
I'm the one that put you undercover...
是我讓你去做臥底...
Stop.
別說了
I may not remember anything,
我也許失憶了
but I know one thing about myself.
但我很了解我自己
Nobody makes me do anything I don't want to.
我不想做的事 沒人能逼我
So, what's our next adventure after this?
這事過後 我們再去哪裏冒險?
How about we stay in one place?
要不我們待在一個地方?
Where are you thinking?
你想去哪兒?
Tokyo.
東京
We always talk about Tokyo.
我們總是談到東京
Tokyo it is.
那就東京吧
Can I ask you something?
我能問你些事嗎?
How did you know that there would be a car there to break our fall?
你怎麼知道那有輛車能讓我們減速?
I didn't.
我並不知道
Some things you just have to take on faith.
有些事你必須心存信念
Hey, Toretto! You need to hear this
嘿 托雷托! 你得聽聽這個
You guys really think you've won.
你們真以為自己贏了
This code you live by,
你們所遵從的原則
it's the very reason why you weren't even in the game.
正是你們根本沒勝算的原因
I told you exactly what I was gonna do if you didn't walk away, Toretto.
我清楚地告訴過你礙我事的後果 托雷托
Go!
走!
But you didn't listen.
但你沒聽進去
I told you I can reach out and break you whenever I want.
我告訴你我隨時都可以出手讓你崩潰
And I have.
我做到了
Come on.
來吧
- Go.  - No!
- 走  - 不要!
Maybe you should call Mia.
也許你該給米婭打個電話
- Mia?  - Brian!
- 米婭?  - 布萊恩!
Let me go!
放開我!
So, this is how it's gonna go down.
所以事情就是這樣
You're gonna cut me loose from these cuffs,
你們會替我解開手銬
you're gonna hand me the chip,
將芯片交給我
I'm gonna walk out of here and you're not gonna follow.
我要光明正大地走出去 而且你們都不會跟過來
You must be joking.
你在做夢
Look at his face.
看看他的表情
Ask him if I'm joking.
問他我是不是在做夢
One hostage does not outweigh the threat to millions.
區區一個人質相比較數萬人的生命來說無足輕重
I'm sorry, but this changes nothing.
對不起 但這改變不了什麼
It changes everything.
這能改變一切
You tell your men to stand down.
讓你的手下把槍放下
Stand down.
把槍放下
Toretto,
托雷托
I need you to know,
我要你清楚
the moment we let him walk out that door with that chip,
一旦我們讓他帶著芯片走出這扇門後
words like "amnesty" and "pardon"
像"赦免"和"特赦"這種許諾
walk out with him.
也跟他一起走了
Those words went out the day we were born.
我們生下來那天開始就不需要這些
Coming, babe?
來嗎 寶貝
Of course.
當然
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
我可不想錯過好戲
Like I said,
就像我說的
you were never in the game.
你根本沒勝算
If I see you on the horizon, I'll make the call and the girl's dead.
要是我待會看到你們 我會打電話過去 那姑娘就死定了
So, what about Toretto's sister?
托雷托的妹妹怎麼辦?
There's no need for her anymore.
她已經沒有價值了
I just jammed every signal up and down the spectrum.
我剛剛屏蔽了整個基地的信號
Let's move.
我們行動吧
I'm coming with you.
我跟你們一起去
Where the hell does this dude think he's going?
他以為他在什麼地方撒野?
We're on an army base, he's trapped.
我們是在陸軍基地 他被困住了
Wow, you just had to open your mouth.
哇 你非得說個不停
Now we got a big-ass plane to deal with.
現在又來了架大飛機了
That ain't a plane. That's a planet.
那不是飛機 那是個星球
打開貨艙門
She's as good as dead if Shaw gets away on that plane.
要是肖上了飛機 那她就死定了
Then we don't let him get away.
那我們就攔住他
Let's end this thing.
結束一切吧
Ride or die.
拼死一搏
Tell them to take off!
讓他們起飛!
起飛! 起飛!
重量太大了! 我們還得加速!
Babe, get me under the wing.
寶貝 送我到機翼下面
If I can hit that flap, we can keep it from taking off.
我要是能打中副翼 飛機就起飛不了
You be careful.
你小心點
This is who we are.
這才是我們的生活
Shit!
混蛋!
外面怎麼回事?
Grab the wheel!
抓好方向盤!
Dom!
唐!
Go!
走!
Come on. Let's go.
快點 我們走
Get in the car.
上車
Whoo!
哇哦!
速度夠了! 我們起飛!
What happened? Did you hit the flap?
怎麼回事? 你打中副翼了嗎?
Uh...
呃...
you should buckle up right now.
你現在該系好安全帶
What?
什麼?
Hey!
嘿!
Wrong team, bitch.
站錯隊了 婊子
Shit.
我操
Yeah!
中了!
I got you.
抓到你了
他們打中副翼了 正在把我們往下拽
往上拉! 往上拉!
Tej!
泰吉!
Keep her steady!
開穩點!
We gotta move, it's going down! Go!
我們得走了 飛機要墜毀了! 快點!
Go, now!
快走 快!
Come on, let's move, move, move!
快點 快跳 跳啊!
Come on!
快點!
Dom!
唐!
Where's Gisele?
吉賽爾在哪?
So this is worth billions, huh?
所以這價值數億 是嗎?
Yes, it is.
對 沒錯
Name your price, Dom.
你開個價吧 唐
1327.
1327號
Don't burn it this time. Please?
這次別再燒焦了 好嗎?
I never go and burn it, man.
我從來不幹這事 哥們
Good food.
吃得不錯
The air quality here is lousy, the traffic is bad,
這裏的空氣很惡心 交通也很爛
but I think you'll learn to like this place.
但我覺得你會學著愛上這裏
Yeah, and here you've got your own garage
沒錯 這也有你自己的車庫
so you can build a car with Daddy.
所以你可以和老爹一起造車
We'll be building a car?
我們要一起造車?
First car better be a Charger, Jack.
第一輛最好是道奇 傑克
You mean Skyline.
你是說日產天際線
Like I said, he's a Toretto.
我說過 他是個托雷托家的人
You're confusing the kid.
你在誤導孩子
Mia, you're gonna let him get away with this?
米婭 你能讓他拋棄這些嗎?
You're really going to do it?
你真的打算這樣?
Tokyo.
東京
Yeah, it's just something I gotta do.
對 有些事必須去做
You know we got your back, whenever you need us.
只要你需要我們 我們都會支持你
Hey, Mia, you better hide your baby oil.
嘿 米婭 你最好把嬰兒油藏起來
I'm just playing.
我就開個玩笑
You better hide that big-ass forehead.
你最好把你的大腦門藏起來
I was just joking, but whatever.
我就開個玩笑 算了 無所謂
Definitely not that funny.
絕不是好事
It's official.
這次是正式的
You're all free.
你們都自由了
Mmm. Mmm.
嗯 嗯
It wasn't half bad, having you work for me.
有你替我幹活非常棒
We all know you were working for me, Hobbs.
我們都知道是你在替我幹活 霍布斯
Agree to disagree.
各持己見
Thank you.
謝謝
Good luck.
祝你好運
Elena?
伊琳娜?
Letty.
萊蒂
This is gonna be awkward.
肯定很尷尬
- But sexy as hell.  - Sexy as hell.
- 但非常性感啊  - 性感異常
I wanted to thank you for everything you've done for him.
我要謝謝你為他做的一切
For us.
為我們
It takes an amazing woman.
你是個了不起的女人
He's an amazing guy.
他是個了不起的男人
Yeah, he is.
沒錯 他是的
Try to keep him out of trouble, huh?
盡力讓他遠離麻煩 好嗎?
Now, you know that's not gonna happen.
你知道那是不可能的
I know.
我明白
Not bad for a cop.
對警察來說不錯
I never thought I'd trust a criminal.
我從沒想過我會相信罪犯
Until next time.
直到下一次
Elena.
伊琳娜
You know you don't have to go.
要知道你沒有必要走
All this... this is your family.
所有這些... 這都是你的家
It's who you are.
這就是原來的你
This is my family.
這也是我的家
This is who I am.
這也是原來的我
All right, everybody, let's eat.
好吧 大家開吃吧
Want some help with that?
需要幫忙嗎?
It's all here, it's done.
到此為止 結束了
Come on, man, let's get with it.
來吧 我們動作快點
First bite, he's got grace.
他吃了第一口 他來說禱告詞
House rules, man. House rules.
家規 老兄 這是家規
Any of this feel familiar to you?
你對這裏熟悉的感覺嗎?
No.
沒有
But it feels like home.
但這感覺就像家
That's good enough for me.
對我來說夠棒了
All right, y'all. Come on, let's do this.
好吧 你們都來 我們祈禱吧
Okay, Roman,
好了 羅曼
bless our table.
說餐前禱告詞吧
Father, thank you for the gathering of friends.
主啊 感謝你讓我們朋友團聚
Father, we give thanks for all the choices we've made,
主啊 感謝我們曾做過的選擇
because that's what makes us who we are.
因為那些成就了今日的我們
Let us forever cherish the loved ones we've lost along the way.
讓我們永遠珍惜一路上我們痛失的愛人
Thank you for the little angel,
感謝小天使的降臨
the newest addition to our family.
為我們的家族又添新丁
Thank you for bringing Letty home.
感謝你帶萊蒂回家
And most of all, thank you for fast cars.
最重要的是 感謝您賜予我們飛車
-=聖城家園SCG字幕組 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
僅供翻譯交流使用, 禁止用於商業用途
協調: 瀟妹紙
翻譯: 咳嗽的小魚 Young 撈鹽 沒看過的一橫 噹噹要變瘦 尤蘭達子 曉笛 袋蜀
校對: 影子
東京
全體注意
有兩輛車正在和一輛RX-7賽跑
比賽正向澀穀中心進行
RX-7正在接近十字路口
Dominic Toretto.
多米尼克·托雷托
You don't know me,
你還不認識我
but you're about to.
但馬上就會的